尴尬的无言以对
Awkward silence.
谢尔顿盯着手机
Sheldon on his phone.
无任何身体接触
No touching.
有人今晚约会哟
Somebody's having date night.
其实现实比看上去色情多了
It's actually steamier than it looks.
谢尔顿正在查文艺复兴时期画作中用于象征
Sheldon's looking up the phallic symbolism of root vegetables
性器官的根菜类蔬菜
in Renaissance paintings.
不是  我刚才看无聊了
Oh, no, I got bored with that.
现在是在网上看剪指甲表皮的剪刀
I'm just browsing cuticle scissors on Amazon.
你怎么能忍得住把他按倒在桌上
How do you not tear off his clothes
扯破他衣服的冲动呢
and take him right here on this table?
你要这么做了  我一定尖叫
If you do that, I'll scream.
谢尔顿  我有个好消息要跟你说
Sheldon, I have some exciting news to tell you.
真巧  我也是
That makes two of us.
我的剪指甲表皮的剪刀将会在
My new cuticle scissors will be here
一到两个工作日内寄到
in one to two business days.
保佑一天就到
Come on, one.
我被邀请去你们大学为一项研究
I've been invited to consult on an experiment
当几个月的顾问
at your university for a few months.
是不是很棒呀
Isn't that great?
我们可以一起共进午餐
We could have lunch together.
一起开车上下班
We could carpool.
最近搭莱纳德的车
You know, riding with Leonard
的确是开始无聊沉闷了
has gotten a little tedious lately.
他唯一有兴趣玩的车上游戏
Th-The only car game he ever wants to play
就是闭嘴游戏
is the Quiet Game.
而且他一点都不会玩
And he's terrible at it.
每次都是我赢
I always win.
所以你没意见吧
So, you're okay with this?
我为什么会有意见
Well, why wouldn't I be?
这项工作会让我们的
Well, this project would have us working
工作地点很接近彼此
in close proximity to one another.
但不是有一句坊间俗谚说
And there's the vulgar adage
"别在自己吃饭的地方拉屎"[兔子不吃窝边草]
that one should not defecate where one eats.
我爸爸以前也老说这句话
My father used to say that all the time.
还有这句  "我是得用嘴帮谁爽一发
That and, um, "Who does one have to orally gratify
才能有人给我上酒啊"
to get a drink around here?"
但那句俗谚跟
But what does that have to do
你来我大学工作有何关系
with you working at the university?
谢尔顿"别在吃饭的地方拉屎"
Sheldon, "Don't defecate where you eat,"
就是指别在工作场所发展男女关系
means don't have a romantic relationship in the workplace.
是这意思吗
Really?
是的
Yes.
我一直都是按字面理解
Yeah, I always took it literally.
所以我从来没有在这间或任何一间餐厅里
That's why I have never once moved my bowels
上过一次大号
in this or any restaurant.
听到你对我们在一起工作没有意见
I'm relieved that you don't have a problem
我心情就放松许多了
with us working together.
我马上就会比你更"放松"了
Not as relieved as I'm about to be.
美丽的新世界啊  小姑娘
It's a brave new world, little lady.
源自奥尔德斯·赫胥黎的小说《美丽的新世界》
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
跟女朋友在一个地方工作  你会后悔的
You don't want your girlfriend at work with you.
地狱蛤蜊
Hell Clam.
有何不可
Why not?
多毛仙女
Hairy Fairy.
我觉得也可能很浪漫啊
I think it could be romantic.
我爸妈就是在我爸工作的地方相遇的
You know, my parents met at his place of work.
你爸是个妇科医生啊
Your father's a gynecologist.
我知道啊
I know.
从子宫颈抹片检查发展到约会
What started as a pap smear turned into a date.
再发展到我妈去那边上班
Which turned into her working there,
再发展到婚姻  最后发展到互相憎恨
which turned into marriage, which then turned into hatred,
然后一直保持到现在
which continues to this day.
双目独眼巨人
Two-Eyed Cyclops.
你能告诉他为什么这是个坏主意吗
Would you please tell him this isn't a good idea?
不啊  我觉得这是好事
No, no, I think it'll be great.
下次他在上班的时候染了结膜炎
Maybe next time he gets conjunctivitis at work,
她会代替我去扶着他的头  帮他滴眼药水
she can hold his head and try to put the drops in his eyes.
没用的东西[大婴儿]
Giant baby.
那是狂暴食人魔卡
That's a Raging Ogre.
我知道啊
Yeah, I know.
像我就绝对不会想跟伯纳黛特一起工作
I'm just saying, I'd never want to work with Bernadette.
你们能想象跟某人整天待在一起
Can you imagine seeing someone all day long
下班之后还得继续黏在一起的生活吗
and then you're supposed to hang out with them after work, too?
等等  我跟你就这样啊
Hold on. We do that all the time.
我跟你一起上班  下班后一起玩
You and I work together and play together.
所以我才投入了另一个女人的怀抱
I know, and it drove me into the arms of another woman.
躁郁熊
Bipolar Bear.
我谢谢你们为我担心
Well, I appreciate your concern,
但我跟艾米见面的时间不会因此加长
but I won't be seeing any more of Amy than I already do.
我们每周相聚时间的配额
I assume we'll deduct any extra time we spend together
会扣掉工作见面的时间
at work from our weekly quota.
你对她说这话的时候  记得叫上我
Please let me be there when you tell her that.
为啥  你想看看艾米听到
Why? So you can see the look on Amy's face
我天才般点子时的表情吗
when she hears my top-notch idea?
求你  求你了  一定要让我去膜拜
Please, oh, please, just let me be there.
艾米  你在加州理工的项目是什么
So, Amy, what are you gonna be working on at Caltech?
我要带一个
I'm leading a study to see
单胺氧化酶的缺乏是否会使猴子
if deficiency of the monoamine oxidase enzyme
恐惧能力瘫痪的研究
leads to paralyzing fear in monkeys.
如果它们跟人一样  那答案就是"是"
If they're anything like humans, the answer's yes.
等等  你在人身上做过这个研究吗
Wait, you've-you've done this experiment on humans?
你是指在再无可失的死刑犯身上做这实验吗
You mean like death row inmates with nothing to lose?
当然没有  那太没职业道德了
No, that would be unethical.
很多人都不知道这件事
You know, not a lot of people know this,
但"单胺氧化酶"
but the monoamine oxidase enzyme
是由玛丽·伯恩海姆这位女性发现的
was discovered by a woman, Mary Bernheim.
没错
That's right.
我的手机就跟你们俩一样聪明
My phone is just as smart as you guys.
艾米  伯纳黛特  佩妮
Amy, Bernadette, Penny.
他一辈子都要这样敲门吗
He's never gonna stop doing that, is he?
我不介意
I don't mind.
希望有天能把他的重复强迫症
I'm hoping to put his love of repetition
引导到"好的地方"上呢
to good use someday.
你好啊
Hi. Um...
我重新考虑过了
I've reconsidered.
你不能来我那边上班
Uh, you can't work where I work.
祝你们今晚愉快
Enjoy the rest of your evening.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
我合同都签了
I-I already signed the contract.
钱我也领了
I cashed a check.
那之后你是不会有好果子吃了
You are not going to come out of this looking good.
谢尔顿  我不懂了
Sheldon, I don't understand.
你之前不是说你可以接受吗
I thought you said you were fine with it.
我之前是啊
Well, I was.
但那是在霍华德跟我解释
But that was before Howard explained to me
如果他要跟他的伴侣一起工作
how awful it would be if he had to work
会有多难受之前
with his significant other.
他说什么
He said what?
不要觉得被侮辱了
Now, don't be insulted.
他只是觉得跟你相处时间过长
He just thinks too much of you
会感觉大脑麻痹  无聊至极
would be mind-numbingly tedious.
失陪一下  我要去跟我老公谈谈
Excuse me, I need to have a chat with my husband.
好吧  保持对话简洁
Yeah, well, now, well... keep it short.
从我听到的来看  说话简洁对你有利
Fr-From what I gather, brevity is your friend.
那我们俩没事吧
So, are we good here?
不  怎么可能没事
No, we're not good here.
从现在开始  我要研究这个项目
I am working on this project.
而且你怎么能对她颐指气使呢
Yeah, and you can't tell her what she can and cannot do.
上周你叫莱纳德不许穿
Last week, you told Leonard he couldn't wear
星战伍基人外套上街
his Wookiee jacket out in public.
这不一样
That's different.
我才不要跟一个穿着
I'm not going to the mall with
白痴太空熊外套的人逛街
someone dressed dumb space bear.
谢尔顿  你不用担心我会去烦你
Sheldon, you don't have to worry about me bothering you.
我不会在你的大楼里工作
I'll be in a different building.
我们也不用一起共进午餐
And we don't even have to have lunch together.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yes.
毕竟我是个科学家
Before all things, I'm a scientist.
我去那里是以工作为先  如果幸运的话
I'm just there to do my work and, with a little luck,
希望能吓"屎"几个猴子
scare the living crap out of some monkeys.
你确定以你飞蛾扑火的性格
You sure your mothlike personality won't be drawn
你不会被我这熊熊的烈火所吸引吗
to this blazing fire that is myself?
确定肯定以及一定
More and more sure.
好吧  我准了
Well, then, you have my permission.
我才不需要你的准许
I didn't ask for your permission.
晚了  我话都说完了
Too late. No backsies.
不是的  你听我说  谢尔顿理解错了
No, no, listen to me. Sheldon misunderstood.
我的意思是
What I meant was,
如果我们一起工作
if we worked together,
我怕你老看到我会嫌烦
there'd be too much of me for you,
而不是我烦你
not the other way around.
霍华德  如果你要骗自己老婆的话
Howard, if you're going to lie to your wife,
拜托别用"谢尔顿理解错了"这句话开头
don't start the sentence with "Sheldon misunderstood."
这样她肯定知道你在撒谎
That's a dead giveaway.
那是怎样
Well?
好吧  好吧
Okay, fine.
我的确那么说了  而且我说的是实话
I did say that, and I think it's true.
我觉得如果我们一起工作又一起生活
I think if we worked together and lived together,
肯定会对彼此产生厌倦之情
we'd get sick of each other.
没错  公平来说  他只是说
Yeah, but to be fair, he only said the part
他自己会烦你
about him getting sick of you.
看在上帝的份上  你为何要置我于死地
For the love of God, why?!
你到底觉得你会烦我哪点
What exactly do you think you'd get sick of?
他想逃过一劫  除了装心脏病发
His only options here are to fake a heart attack
就只能真的心脏病发了
or have a real one.
没有特别哪点啦  我
It-it's nothing in particular. I...
是我的声音吗  还是我太蛮横了
Is it my voice? Am I too bossy?
我的手臂突然麻了
My arm is feeling numb.
说中了吧
Nailed it.
心脏病发不是这只手臂麻  蠢货
That's the wrong arm for a heart attack, doofus.
我的重点是  我觉得如果我们整天在一起
My point is, I'm sure there are things about me
我的某些方面肯定会
that would drive you crazy if you had to deal
惹你生气的
with them all day long.
比如说看着我的眼睛对我撒谎吗
Like looking me in the eye and lying to me?
拜托  我只是
Oh, well, come on, I just...
不然我撒谎的时候  眼睛要看哪里啊
Where am I supposed to look when I lie to you?
今晚跟别人睡去吧
Find somewhere else to sleep tonight.
妮妮
Oh, Bernie...
如果能让你觉得好过点的话
If it makes you feel any better,
我和艾米相安无事
Amy and I are fine.
我是说  非常好的那种
I mean, really good.
小伙子们  昨晚的睡衣派对如何
So, boys, how was the pajama party?
你们俩是不是跳上床  拿梳子当麦克风唱歌呀
You guys jump on the bed and sing into hair brushes?
那才不是什么睡衣派对
It wasn't a pajama party.
只不过是两个好兄弟待在一起  说说笑笑
It was just a couple of bros hanging out, giggling,
边吃甜甜圈  边看《公主新娘》
eating cookie dough and watching Princess Bride.
1987年的浪漫爱情奇幻电影
拜托  别说了
Please, stop talking.
遵命[出自电影]
As you wish.
谢尔顿  如果不是我为了帮你
I mean, you know, Sheldon, none of this would've happened
就不会落到今天如此田地
if I hadn't tried to help you.
如果早期的宇宙
Uh, it also wouldn't have happened
宇宙大爆炸后  宇宙中的物质几乎全部都是氢原子和氦原子
氢多一点或是少一点
if, in the early universe,
到了后来经历过恒星的原子核聚变反应
这些轻元素才转化为如今宇宙中存在的所有其他重元素
今天也不会有我们的存在  更不会发生这件事
hydrogen was a little more common or a little less common.
真有意思  换你举例了
This is fun. Your turn.
-你们好  -艾米好呀
- Gentlemen. - Hey, Amy.
你好
Hello.
艾米态度很冷淡啊
That was kind of icy.
你们俩没事吧
You two okay?
我们当然没事
Oh, we're fine.
正如霍华德建议的那样
As Howard advised,
她只是尊重我们的专业界限而已
she's merely respecting our professional boundaries.
真明智
Smart.
居然听取昨晚帮
Take relationship advice from a man
拉杰绑辫子的男人的建议
who spent last night braiding Raj's hair.
也是  你说得有道理
Yeah, you make a good point.
感觉好像我的担忧是多余的
It would appear I was worried for nothing.
瞧瞧她  超级不情愿
Look at her, desperately wishing
坐在那边  一心想过来酷哥的桌子
she was over here at the cool table.
别担心  小飞蛾
Don't worry, little moth.
烈火哥来救你了
The flame will come to you.
万一
On the off chance that
伯纳黛特真的不打电话来道歉
Bernadette doesn't call back and apologize,
那我们今晚吃墨西哥餐如何
how do you feel about Mexican food for dinner tonight?
我不知道  听着挺重口的
I-I don't know. Sounds kind of heavy.
那是因为你总是吃薯片
That's 'cause you always fill up on chips.
这位是来自斯德哥尔摩的冈德森博士
And this is Dr. Gunderson from Stockholm.
瑞典呀
Ah, Sweden.
是我最喜欢的木偶
Yeah, home of my favorite Muppet
和第二喜欢的肉丸[宜家肉丸]的家乡
and, uh, second favorite meatball.
好吧  果然北欧人没有幽默感的名声是真的
Okay, the Nordic reputation for lack of humor is well-founded.
天啊  他是叫冈德森还是干得瘆呀
Boy, is his name Gunderson or No-Funderson?
你到底想要说什么  库珀博士
Where are we going with this, Dr. Cooper?
拜托  我是你的男朋友
Oh, please, I'm your boyfriend.
你应该叫我谢尔顿
You call me Sheldon.
没错  我跟这位穿着毛衣的小可爱
That's right, I am in a boy-girl relationship
是男女朋友关系
with this cute little lump of wool.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
而且还有身体接触哦
It's a physical relationship, too.
比如说  拉手  拥抱  即使在大热天也是
Hand-holding, hugging... even on hot days.
好吧  又多了一种
Okay, here's a new one.
显然现在我们在桌子下
Apparently now we kick each other
互踢彼此的小腿
in the shin under the table.
换我踢你了  你觉得如何
How do you like it when I do it to you?
不是很爽  对吧
Not so much, huh?
测试实验品D7
Test subject D7,
又名贝琪  恐惧反应研究
aka Betsy, fear response study.
一号图片
Image number one:
法国人骑着自行车载着长棍面包
Frenchman on bicycle carrying baguettes.
无可见反应
No visible reaction.
二号图片  苏萨大号
Image number two: sousaphone.
还是没反应
Still no reaction.
好吧
Okay.
那我们升级一下图片
Let's kick things up a notch.
三号图片
Image number three:
一只满嘴猴子的鳄鱼
crocodile with a mouthful of monkeys.
好的  总算有点反应了
Okay, now we're talking.
福勒博士
Dr. Fowler?
你来干嘛  谢尔顿
What do you want, Sheldon?
我下班了  所以
Well, I'm done with work, so...
抱歉  抱歉
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
真是不好意思
Sorry. Uh...
现在好点了吗
Better?
长棍面包
Oh, baguettes.
我喜欢长棍面包
Yes, I like baguettes.
你到底在做什么
What exactly are you doing?
通过视觉刺激来测试卷尾猴的反应
Determining baseline fear levels in capuchin monkeys
从而界定他们的恐惧等级
by measuring their response to visual stimuli.
所以你游手好闲着
So, goofing off.
我刚说了
As I was saying,
我下班了  而莱纳德还没
I'm done with work and Leonard's not.
所以好消息是  你可以送我回家
So good news, you get to take me home.
如果你把我哄高兴了
Play your cards right,
我就让你载着我经过
I'll let you drive me past the lot
那个晚上停公车的停车场
where the buses park at night.
我现在走不开  谢尔顿
I can't leave now, Sheldon.
我很忙
I'm very busy.
再说了  你在餐厅那样对我之后
Besides, why would I want to do you a favor
我干嘛还要帮你的忙
after the way you treated me in the cafeteria?
四号图片  蟒蛇
Image number four: boa constrictor.
你到底在说什么
What on earth are you talking about?
我在餐厅的行为多讨人喜欢呀
My behavior in the cafeteria was delightful.
或许你朋友冈德森需要
Maybe your friend Gunderson needs
去宜家  组装点幽默感回来
to head over to IKEA and assemble a sense of humor.
我第一天上班  你就当着我同事的面
You embarrassed me in front of my colleagues
让我下不了台
on my first day here.
五号图像
Image number five:
茶杯里的小猫咪
kitten in a teacup.
-我让你丢人了  -算了
- Oh... embarrassed you? - You know what?
我现在没空  你自己想办法回家吧
I don't have time for this. Find another way home.
我怎么感觉你好像在生我的气
I'm starting to get the sense that you're angry with me.
是吗  是什么给了你灵感
Really? What tipped you off?
事实上有不少
Couple things, actually.
你的语气  你的肢体语言
Your tone of voice, your body language...
-快出去  -还有这话
- Get out. - Well, now, that.
六号图像  女性分娩
Image number six: woman giving birth.
都9点了  你去哪里了
It's 9:00. Where you been?
我得坐公车回家
Oh, I had to take the bus home.
睡着了  结果坐过站
Fell asleep and missed my stop.
不是吧
Oh, no.
你们知道洛杉矶有斯里兰卡社区吗
Did you know that Los Angeles has a Little Sri Lanka?
我不知道
I did not.
我现在知道了
Well, I do... now.
他们是非常好的人
They're a lovely people.
不过醒来时和他们脸对脸的  还是挺可怕的
Although terrifying when you wake up face-to-face with them.
如果你们饿  我这里有些
If you're hungry, I brought home
羊肉和椰奶
some mutton and coconut milk.
你为什么买这个  你讨厌羊肉
Why'd you get that? You hate lamb.
我本想问路
I was asking for directions.
显然  我跟他们在沟通上出了问题
Apparently, there was a communication problem.
不是艾米送你回家吗
I thought Amy was gonna drive you home.
我也这样想的
Yeah, I thought so, too,
但她的表现非常奇怪
but she's acting very strangely.
我在公车上和一个斯里兰卡人讨论这个问题
I was discussing it with a Sri Lankan fellow on the bus,
他猜测可能是因为最近有只老虎
and he hypothesized that a tiger may have
从她的影子上跳过去了
recently run across her shadow.
不过他可能只是在为他大舅子的
Although he may have just been trying to drum up business
巫医诊所招揽生意
for his brother-in-law's witch doctor practice.
谢尔顿  你和艾米到底发生什么事了
Okay, Sheldon, what happened between you and Amy?
你能相信吗  她说我让她丢人了
Well, can you believe she said I embarrassed her?
相信
Yeah.
但你连事情经过都不知道呢
But you didn't even hear the details.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
我认识你很久了
I've known you a long time,
以下这句话
and I'm going to tell you this
我会用我所有的爱来为之裹糖衣
with all the love I can possibly muster.
艾米是对的  你是错的
Amy's right. You're wrong.
-但你都不知道...  -没必要
- But you don't even know... - Doesn't matter.
-容我说一句  -没必要
- But, now, but in my defense... - Doesn't matter.
你根本没听我的委曲
You're not listening to my side of it.
好吧  谢尔顿  你有什么委曲
Okay, fine, Sheldon. What is your side?
好吧
Well...
不  这次我必须挺艾米
Nope, got to go with Amy on this one.
这虾好辣啊
Shrimp was spicy.
你要抗胃酸咀嚼片吗
You want a TUMS?
有热带水果味吗
You got the tropical fruit kind?
没有  如果我买这种口味的
No, if I buy those,
我会拿来当糖吃
I just go through them like candy.
可不是嘛
Tell me about it.
我发誓我有次拉出了根像粉笔的玩意
One time, I swear I pooped out a stick of chalk.
-我去开  -多谢
- I'll get it. - Thanks.
你好
Hi.
你来啦
Oh, hi.
也许我的反应太夸张了
I may have overreacted.
我自己也没有处理好这次的问题
Yeah, well, I didn't handle it so great, either.
只是有时候我觉得  比起和我在一起
It's just sometimes I feel like you enjoy spending time
你更喜欢和你的朋友们一起玩
with your friends more than with me.
-不是这样的  -不是吗
- That's not true. - It's not?
你们整天工作在一起
You spend all day together at work,
晚上又在一起玩游戏
and then you all hang out at night playing games,
一起去漫画书店
going to the comic book store.
上个星期  你俩还一起去享受了情侣按摩
Last week, you two got a couples massage.
所以你说不想和我在一起
So, when you said you wouldn't want to spend
那么长的时间  真的很伤我的心
that much time with me, it really hurt my feelings.
我明白了
Yeah, no, I get that.
真是对不起
I'm so sorry.
从明天开始  我会洗心革面
Starting tomorrow, I am turning over a new leaf.
我会将与你共度美好时光  摆在第一位
Time with you is my number one priority.
为什么是明天开始
Why tomorrow?
蝙蝠侠的新游戏  我们马上就要打通关了
Well, we're real close to finishing off the new Batman game.
太好玩了
It is awesome.
也许你应该去追她
Uh, you should probably go after her.
我应该去追你吗
Should I go after you?
不用
No!
多谢你让我们夫妻不和
Thanks for getting me in trouble.
艾米
Amy.
谢尔顿  你这么晚过来做什么
Sheldon, what are you doing here so late?
我睡不着  因为我一直在想
I couldn't sleep because I kept thinking
我们之间发生的事
about what happened earlier between us.
而且  我在公车上已经睡够了
Also, I had one heck of a bus nap.
说到这个
Oh, speaking of which,
你要来点羊肉和椰奶吗
do you want some mutton and coconut milk?
不要
No.
这玩意儿怎么白送都没人要
Well, I cannot give this stuff away.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
艾米  这些话很难启齿
Amy, this isn't easy to say.
所有的感情都不会是一帆风顺的
All relationships are difficult,
尤其是对方是一个
but even more so when you're in one
连每天日常的社交活动
with a person who struggles
都要辛苦应对的人
with everyday social interactions.
坦白来说
And frankly...
在某些人眼里
who can strike some people
他就是个怪胎
as being kind of a weirdo.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
你不是怪胎
you're not a weirdo.
我说的不是我
I wasn't speaking about me.
说实话
I mean, honestly,
我真不知道什么事让你这么生气
there's no telling what will set you off.
以男友的身份自我介绍
You know, introducing myself as your boyfriend.
给你开车送我回家的机会
Giving you the opportunity to drive me home.
用种族笑话来打破
Breaking the ice with your colleagues
你与同事的僵局
using ethnic humor,
这是最有意思的幽默感了
the funniest kind of humor.
你到底想说什么
What's your point?
我想说  我们是情侣
My point is, we're a couple.
还有
And...
我喜欢的是真实的你
I like you for who you are.
怪异什么的都接受
Quirks and all.
我也喜欢你
I like you, too.
那是自然
Well, I should hope so.
还有谁会这个时候来敲门
I don't see anyone else banging on this door
容忍你的这一堆废话
to put up with your nonsense.
连再见都不说吗
Not even a good-bye?
就是因为这样
You see, that's the kind of thing
才让别人觉得你是个怪胎
that makes people think you're weird.
可怜的孩子
Poor kid.
她怎么就这么没自知自明呢
She just doesn't see it.
我不会跟霍华德道歉的
I'm not apologizing to Howard.
我要他跪着来求我
He can come beg me on his knees.
谢尔顿也一样
Sheldon, too.
如果在工作时见到他  我会把他当空气
If I see him at work, I'm just going to ignore him.
不用担心  我跟莱纳德说了
All right, don't worry. I talked to Leonard.
他会让你们家男人乖乖坐下  好好教育他们
He is gonna sit the guys down and set them straight.
激光已加热
Laser's warmed up.
放气球
Pull!